Hallelujah!
It is time for in-searching for your heart.
My hands are blessed with the blessing of the Lord
Everything I touch
Surely must be blessed
My hands are filled
With the blessing of the Lord
Let me find your heart.
Let me find your heart, your appearance can be deceptive.
You look as if you are laughing whereas you are not laughing.
You look as if you believe, you do not believe. You look as if you're here, you are no here.
Let me see your heart. Let me find your heart.
Faith is of man's heart.
Your heart!
Let your heart contact the Holy Spirit,
your heart contact God.
My heart, speak to the Holy Spirit.
Find the Holy Spirit.
When your heart is at rest, you are at home.
You are at home, when your heart is at rest.
My heart!
Search your heart. Are you still holding unforgiveness, resentment,
anger, bad feelings towards anyone
You need a free spirit, a free heart to offer
prayer of faith and prayer of faith will heal the sick.
Prayer of faith will set the captives free.
Prayer of faith will bless the poor.
If there is any sin,
you shall be forgiven.
Receive a free heart! - Amen!
A free spirit! - Amen!
Be free, in the name of Jesus! - Amen!
I want to be like Jesus in my heart.
Tell yourself: I want to be like Jesus in my heart. In Jesus Christ's name we pray! - Amen!
I believe, I'm talking to the free spirit.
Say: "My heart is free". There's no bad feelings towards anyone.
No resentment, no unforgiveness, no anger, in Jesus Christ's name! Amen!
Rejoice! Salvation has come. How will you keep this salvation?
Because this is home, the temple of Holy Ghost without unforgiveness,
resentment, anger, bad feelings towards anyone. Tell your neighbour: "Let your future speak for you. Be patient
for your future." Yes, you are to be patient for your future.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Patient for your future. Right now, you want to cleanse the house.
Let the power of the Lord come down
Let the power of the Lord from Heaven above Let the power of the Lord come down
Do not forget that this is not a song, it is tongue to Heaven. You are speaking to Heaven,
with all your heart - it is a prayer, not just a song. Wherever demon is hiding in your life!
Out!
Right now begin to rebuke that demon out of your life.
Out of my life!
You demon!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! The name Jesus is above all. Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ! - Amen!
Jesus Christ! - Amen! - Above all! Jesus Christ! - Amen!
Jesus Christ! - Amen! - Above all! - Amen!
Wherever demon is hiding - command them out!
Wherever demon is hiding - I command them out in the name of Jesus!
In your life! In your finances! In your business! In your carrier! In your household!
In your marriage! Say: "Out!"
Say: "Above all powers - Jesus' name!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Above all kings - Jesus Christ!
The Restorer!
The Deliverer!
Thank you!
Thank you, Lord!
Wherever that disease, that sickness, disease in your blood,
in your fluid, in your tendon - command it out! That sickness! That fibroid!
That fibroid! That cancer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
That cancer! That affliction! I say - out!
That fibroid! That affliction! That disease! In the name of Jesus! Amen!
Command it out, command it out!
Watch your screen and see people vomiting out strange substances from their system,
there are poisonous substances that they are vomiting right now in different parts of the church
and even in the overflow sections. Watch your screen, right now, and see what is happening!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen as you are praying! Just a Word!
In the mighty name of Jesus! Say: "Restorer! Restore my life! Restore my health!"
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Strange substances the people are vomiting out, right now. Those are the poisonous substances they have taken
in the dream and at the tables of the enemies. The Holy Spirit is flushing them out right now.
Viewers all over the world, distance is not a barrier. Right now, begin to use your faith to put a demand on the anointing.
In the mighty name of Jesus! I command that affliction! I say -
you affliction! Say: "Out!"
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen! See blood substances in that vomit.
The right hand of God is Power! I command that affliction out! I say - out! That disease, out!
That disease, out! That affliction, out! Prayer!
Continue to watch your screen! You can see the clot of blood in what they are vomiting out.
The root of the problem is what the Spirit of God is casting out right now. Watch the screen.
In the mighty name of Jesus! The name "Jesus" is "the Restorer, the Healer".
I command that sickness in your faculties, in your organs - out! I command them out! I say - out!
Command them out! Open your lips!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Mass Prayer With TB Joshua
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Keep watching the screen and see what people are vomiting out.
Command them! By the Blood of Jesus, I wash away all diseases and sicknesses in your body.
I command them out!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Be set free!
You blood, you are sanctified! You kidney, you are sanctified. You liver, be sanctified,
in the name of Jesus! Your bones, your organs, be sanctified in the name of Jesus.
Be sanctified, in the name of Jesus! In the mighty name of Jesus!
Begin to rise again! Rise again! Your bones, rise again! Your kidney, rise again!
Your liver, rise again! Your blood, rise again! Your bones, rise again! Your tendons, rise again!
Rise again! Your organs, rise again! Open your lips and begin to confess your freedom.
Say: "I'm living in my confession. I am walking in my confession." Yes! What you confess, so shall it be!
Right now, begin to live in your confession. Live in your confession. Walk in your confession.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Do you want to hear your position now? You are free!
Let me speak to you clearly, all I hear about you now - breakthrough!
Do you want to hear clearly? - Yes! - Breakthrough! In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
I cover you with the blood of Jesus! Be covered with the blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray! Hallelujah! Let us pray for your nations, your countries, the whole world.
Raise it up! God 's intervention! Open your lips, pray for your nations, your countries.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray! Open your lips and begin to release your nations from whatever spirit that
is tormenting your country: idolatry, corruption, misrule, misjudge, keeling, stealing, destruction. Prayer!
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name we pray! I cannot hear you! - Amen!
With all your heart, agree: Jesus loves me. Say to yourself. If Jesus loves you - what follows?
No one can come against you. Come to that resolution right now! Say: "Jesus loves me, as He loves any
of His apostles." Yes, come to that conclusion: "Jesus loves me." If Jesus loves you, just as He loves any of
His apostles, what follows? - No one can be against me! - I cannot hear you! Hallelujah!
For those who are knowing Jesus for the first time, those of us who want to rededicate ourselves -
say after me: "Lord Jesus, come into my heart, wash me with Your precious Blood, make me Your channel
of shining light, a channel of purity, a channel of faithfulness, a channel of obedience, a channel of humility,
a channel of love. In Jesus Christ's name! Lord Jesus, You died in my place. I believe You died
in my place. And thank You for Your salvation, in Jesus Christ's name! Rejoice! Thank you!
TT: Esther Mwelwa: 17/7/2018
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 21/08/2018